A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1960-1974; 1; 20.4 Cubic Feet 50 document boxes
  - "W", Miscellaneous, 1967-1974 (Box 51, Folder 541)
  - Yankee Stadium, (Yankee-Giants Move to Shea), 1971 (Box 51, Folder 542)
  - Youth, Miscellaneous, (Civil Service, Voting, Student Interns, Labor), 1962-1972 (Box 51, Folder 543)
  - Youth, 18 Year Vote, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 544)
  - Zukosky, Jerome, (Free-lance Journalist and Consultant), 1969 1973 (Box 51, Folder 545)
- Campaign Files, Presidential, 1958-1968; 2; 6.8 Cubic Feet 18 document boxes
  This subseries has speeches, articles, television and radio campaign materials, press releases, and informational pieces used for Rockefeller's bids for the U.S. presidency in 1964 and 1968. It also contains documentation onthe the 1965 New York mayoral campaign.
  - Campaign Speeches, Summaries of Speeches, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 546)
  - Campaign Speeches, Index by Subjects, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 547)
  - Campaign Promises By Rockefeller in 1958, By Subject (Box 52, Folder 548)
  - Campaign Key Rockefeller Statements, Indexed by Subject, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 549)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics, "Dear Fellow Republican" Letters, 1960 October 31 1960 November 25 (Box 52, Folder 550)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. General Material (Box 52, Folder 551)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. General Material (Box 53, Folder 552)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. Kennedy Material (Box 53, Folder 553)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. Miscellaneous Material, 1959-1962 (Box 53, Folder 554)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. Miscellaneous Material, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 555)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. Nixon Material (Box 53, Folder 556)
  - Campaign 1960, National Politics. TV Material (Box 53, Folder 557)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Articles, Newspapers, Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 558)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Books (Box 53, Folder 559)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Ebony Magazine, Statement, 1963 December 24-1964 (Box 54, Folder 560)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, General Files, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 561)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, General Files (Box 54, Folder 562)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Look Magazine, 1964 May (Box 54, Folder 563)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, North American Newspaper Alliance, "What We Learn from the Common Market Countries", 1963 November-1964 (Box 54, Folder 564)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, North American Newspaper Alliance, "The American Farmer and the Common Market, 1963 November-1964 (Box 54, Folder 565)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, North American Newspaper Alliance, "Our Overseas Dollar Drain and What We Must Do About It" November 1963, 1963 November-1964 (Box 54, Folder 566)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, New York Times Magazine "Those Worn-out Labels, Liberals and Conservative" 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 567)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Pageant Article, Senator Jacob Javits, 1964 January 13 (Box 54, Folder 568)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Saturday Evening Post, "Speaking Out" (Box 54, Folder 569)
  - Campaign 1964, National Politics, Conservatives, (Radical Right), 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 570)
  - Debate, (See Also Barry Goldwater), 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 571)
  - Debate, (See Also Barry Goldwater), 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 572)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Domestic Policies, 1963 October-1964 May (Box 55, Folder 573)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Foreign Policies, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 574)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Miscellaneous Files, 1964 May-July (Box 55, Folder 575)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Miscellaneous Files, 1964 April-May (Box 55, Folder 576)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Miscellaneous Files, 1964 January-April (Box 55, Folder 577)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Miscellaneous Files, 1964 October-December (Box 56, Folder 578)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Miscellaneous Files, 1963 June-October (Box 56, Folder 579)
  - Javits, Jacob, Senator, New York Times, Reprint, 1963 October 27 (Box 56, Folder 580)
  - Johnson, Lyndon, President, Election Memos, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 581)
  - Kennedy, John F. President, Miscellaneous Files, Eulogies, Statements, 1963 February-1964 October (Box 56, Folder 582)
  - Kennedy, John F. President, Miscellaneous Files, Statements, 1962 January-October (Box 56, Folder 583)
  - Literature, 1964 Campaign, (Brochures and Memos) (Box 56, Folder 584)
  - Literature, 1964 Campaign, (Press Kit) (Box 56, Folder 585)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, (Biography), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 586)
  - Messages, Telegrams suggested for 1964 Campaign, 1964 February-March (Box 57, Folder 587)
  - National Politics-Miscellaneous 1964, (Editorials, newspaper clippings, Memos, Press Releases) (Box 57, Folder 588)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 589)
  - Newspaper Columns, Miscellaneous Political, 1959-1964 (Box 57, Folder 590)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (His comments on political issues), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 591)
  - Perkins, Roswell B. Miscellaneous memos and statements, 1974 May 6-1964 June 17 (Box 57, Folder 592)
  - Perkins, Roswell B. Miscellaneous memos and statements, 1964 April 30-May 5 (Box 57, Folder 593)
  - Perkins, Roswell B. Miscellaneous memos and statements, 1964 April 13-27 (Box 57, Folder 594)
  - Perkins, Roswell B. Miscellaneous memos and statements, 1964 March 16-April 9 (Box 58, Folder 595)
  - Perkins, Roswell B. Miscellaneous memos on strategy, research And positions, speech drafts, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 596)
  - Personnel, Resumes, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 597)
  - Platform-Republican, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 598)
  - Platform-Republican, Background Documents, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 599)
  - Platform-Republican, Analysis Notebook, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 600)
  - Poll, General, Major Issues, 1960-1964 (Box 58, Folder 601)
  - Presidential-1964, Primaries, Conventions, Schedules (Box 58, Folder 602)
  - Press Releases, Campaign, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 603)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Biography, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 604)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Image, 1962-1963 (Box 59, Folder 605)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Introduction for Speeches, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 606)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Memos, Miscellaneous, etc., 1964 (Box 59, Folder 607)
  - Scranton, William A. (Governor of Pennsylvania) Comparisons Of Republican Candidates, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 608)
  - Senate Race-General, (Keating-Kennedy), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 609)
  - T.V. Radio Spots, 1964 Campaign (Box 59, Folder 610)
  - T.V. Radio Spots, 1964 Campaign, Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 611)
  - T.V. Radio Spots, 1964 Campaign, Transcripts-Remarks by Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 612)
  - T.V. Radio Spots, 1964 Campaign, "The Monitor Interview" with Barry Goldwater and Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1964 May 15 (Box 59, Folder 613)
  - 1964 Campaign, California, (memos, briefs, press releases) (Box 59, Folder 614)
  - 1964 Campaign, California, (memos, briefs, press releases) (Box 59, Folder 615)
  - 1964 Campaign, California, (memos, press releases, survey) (Box 60, Folder 616)
  - 1964 Campaign, Hawaii, (press release), 1964 December 18 (Box 60, Folder 617)
  - 1964 Campaign, Maryland, (statement by Mayor Theodore McKeldin), 1963 November 12 (Box 60, Folder 618)
  - 1964 Campaign, Midwest Region, (press release), 1964 January 11 (Box 60, Folder 619)
  - 1964 Campaign, Missouri, (economic highlights) (Box 60, Folder 620)
  - 1964 Campaign, New England Region, (press releases on James Oakes), 1974 January 11 (Box 60, Folder 621)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (primary, Loeb, press releases, polls clippings), 1963 September 21-1964 March 11 (Box 60, Folder 622)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (newspapers, general), 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 623)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Taft University-Murry Snyder), 1963 (Box 60, Folder 624)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 1. "Why I am Running"), 1964 January (Box 60, Folder 625)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 2. "We Need 20 Million New Jobs"), 1964 January (Box 60, Folder 626)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 3. "We Must have Fiscal Integrity"), 1964 January (Box 60, Folder 627)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 4. "The Goldwater Threat to Social Security"), 1964 February (Box 60, Folder 628)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 5. "How to Meet the Communist Challenge"), 1964 February (Box 60, Folder 629)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 6. "Helping Small Business Grow"), 1964 February (Box 60, Folder 630)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 7. "Keeping Government Close to the People"), 1964 February (Box 60, Folder 631)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column 8. "What Your Vote Can Mean on Primary Day"), 1964 March (Box 61, Folder 632)
  - 1964 Campaign, New Hampshire, (Column for University of New Hampshire Student Paper), 1963 October (Box 61, Folder 633)
  - 1964 Campaign, Ohio, Memo, 1963 October 14 (Box 61, Folder 634)
  - 1964 Campaign, Oregon, Memos, Remarks, 1963 December 29-1964 May 14 (Box 61, Folder 635)
  - 1964 Campaign, Rhode Island, Press Release, 1964 January 30 (Box 61, Folder 636)
  - 1964 Campaign, South Dakota, Memos, 1963 April 30 (Box 61, Folder 637)
  - 1964 Campaign, Utah, Editorial, 1963 November 4 (Box 61, Folder 638)
  - 1964 Campaign, Washington DC Telegram Draft, 1964 March 5 (Box 61, Folder 639)
  - 1964 Campaign, Washington Sate, Memos and Letters, 1963 October-November (Box 61, Folder 640)
  - 1964 Campaign, West Virginia, Press Releases, Memos, Editorials, 1963 September-1964 May (Box 61, Folder 641)
  - 1964 Campaign, Wisconsin, Draft of Telegrams, Memos, 1963 October-1964 March (Box 61, Folder 642)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, John Lindsey, 1965 August-November (Box 61, Folder 643)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, John Lindsey, 1965 March-August (Box 61, Folder 644)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, John Lindsey Papers, (Transportation, Crime, Housing, Health, Education, Civil Rights, Narcotics), 1965 October-1966 (Box 61, Folder 645)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Dick Gregory, Negro Politics, Riots in Los Angeles (Box 61, Folder 646)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, John Lindsey (Box 61, Folder 647)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 648)
    Scope and Contents note
    Memoranda, Miscellaneous.
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965 July-1966 November (Box 62, Folder 649)
    Messages from Nelson A. Rockefeller to Various Groups, Telegrams, etc.
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, O'Connor, Frank, Candidate (was State Senator) for Governor, 1965 September-1966 October (Box 62, Folder 650)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Pamphlets, etc. (Box 62, Folder 651)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Research Materials-Health Speech, 1965 March-1966 (Box 62, Folder 652)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Research Materials-Human Interest, (Letter to Nelson A. Rockefeller) (Box 62, Folder 653)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Research Materials-Issues, Miscellaneous Information on Various Subjects A-Z (Box 62, Folder 654)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Research Materials-Radio and Television (Box 62, Folder 655)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Sample Introductions of Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1965-1966, undated (Box 63, Folder 656)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Speeches, Miscellaneous, on Various Subjects for Various People (Box 63, Folder 657)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965 March-1966 May (Box 63, Folder 658)
    Speeches, Stock Speeches-Health.
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, Speeches, Stock Speeches-Miscellaneous, 1965 July-1966 (Box 63, Folder 659)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, "Mechanical Data" (By County), 1965 November-1966 (Box 63, Folder 660)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller / Mayoral Campaign, 1965-1966, "Mechanical Data" (By County) November 1966 Continued, 1966 November (Box 63, Folder 661)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Campaign, Transcripts of News Conferences, Radio and Television, Question and Answer Sessions, September, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 662)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Campaign, Transcripts of News Conferences, Radio and Television, Question and Answer Sessions, 1966 October 6-18 (Box 63, Folder 663)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Campaign, Transcripts of News Conferences, Radio and Television, Question and Answer Sessions, 1966 October 19-31 (Box 63, Folder 664)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Campaign, Transcripts of News Conferences, Radio and Television, Question and Answer Sessions, 1966 November (Box 64, Folder 665)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, B.I.D.S. for Rockefeller, Postcards of Support of Election, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 666)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Bond Issue, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 667)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Candidates, Humphrey, Hubert, 1968 May-July (Box 64, Folder 668)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Candidates, Kennedy, Robert, 1968 May-June (Box 64, Folder 669)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Candidates, Nixon, Richard M., 1968 April-July (Box 64, Folder 670)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Romney, George, 1967 February-November (Box 64, Folder 671)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Campaign Literature (Box 64, Folder 672)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, General File, 1968 June-July (Box 64, Folder 673)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, General File, 1968 March-May (Box 64, Folder 674)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Nixon, Richard, T.V. Spots, 1968 October 2 (Box 64, Folder 675)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Post Convention and Election, 1968 August 21-November 7 (Box 65, Folder 676)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Pre-Convention Communication Strategy, 1968 May 23 (Box 65, Folder 677)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases, New York State Executive Chamber, 1968 October-November (Box 65, Folder 678)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases, New York State Executive Chamber, 1968 September (Box 65, Folder 679)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases, New York State Executive Chamber, 1968 February-May (Box 65, Folder 680)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases, New York State Executive Chamber, 1967 August-1968 January (Box 65, Folder 681)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases, New York News From Rockefeller for President Headquarters, 1968 May-July (Box 65, Folder 682)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Public Relations, Press Releases, Mailings, 1968 March 8-May 10 (Box 65, Folder 683)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Research and Intelligence Report: "Prelude to the Summer Campaign", Material on Nixon and Reagan, 1968 May 28 (Box 65, Folder 684)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Research: Miscellaneous Memos and Policy Papers, 1968 April-May (Box 65, Folder 685)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Research: Organization of Domestic Research Staff, 1968 April-May (Box 65, Folder 686)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Resumes, 1967 December 11-1968 July 30 (Box 66, Folder 687)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Thank - you Letters from Nelson Rockefeller, 1968 June 23-August 30 (Box 66, Folder 688)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Agriculture, 1968 April 2-June 13 (Box 66, Folder 689)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Civil Rights, 1968 May 8-July 5 (Box 66, Folder 690)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Conservation and Recreation, 1968 May 28 (Box 66, Folder 691)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Consumer Protection, 1968 May 8 (Box 66, Folder 692)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Conventional Arms Trade, (George Thayer), 1968 July (Box 66, Folder 693)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, (Mr. Maxwell) Record of Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 June 20 (Box 66, Folder 694)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, The Draft, 1968 April 25-May 25 (Box 66, Folder 695)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Economic Policy, 1967 April 18-1968 May 14 (Box 66, Folder 696)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Education, 1968 May 23 (Box 66, Folder 697)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Environment, 1968 March 12 (Box 66, Folder 698)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Federalism, International Relations, 1968 June 7 (Box 66, Folder 699)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Fiscal Responsibility, 1968 May 28 (Box 66, Folder 700)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Foreign Relations (Vietnam), 1968 January 11-July 13 (Box 66, Folder 701)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Funnies, ("One-Liners" for Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1968 July 15 (Box 66, Folder 702)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, General Speech Ideas, 1968 May 27-July 9 (Box 66, Folder 703)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Government Reorganization, 1968 February 14-May 24 (Box 66, Folder 704)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Health and Mental Health, 1968 July 17 (Box 66, Folder 705)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Humor, undated (Box 66, Folder 706)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Land Use (National) Policy, 1968 February 27-May 21 (Box 66, Folder 707)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Law Enforcement, 1968 January 26-June 14 (Box 67, Folder 708)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Miscellaneous Speeches, 1968 March 18-June 3 (Box 67, Folder 709)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Mitchell Ideas, Rockefeller Acceptance, 1968 June (Box 67, Folder 710)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Nuclear Energy, 1967 December 22-1968 January 9 (Box 67, Folder 711)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Polls, 1968 June 1-July 16 (Box 67, Folder 712)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Poverty, 1968 May 22-June 25 (Box 67, Folder 713)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Presidency Office, 1968 May 7 (Box 67, Folder 714)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Urban Cities, 1968 April 18 (Box 67, Folder 715)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Voting-Votes, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 716)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Youth, 1968 May 7 (Box 67, Folder 717)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Ideas, Welfare, 1968 June 13 (Box 67, Folder 718)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Miscellaneous Drafts Prepared by Speech Writing Staff, 1968 June 15-July 21 (Box 67, Folder 719)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Letters to Fellow Republicans, 1968 May 31-July 22 (Box 67, Folder 720)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Mailings to Republican Influences, 1968 June 12 (Box 67, Folder 721)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Letters to Rockefeller Supporters, 1968 June 3 (Box 67, Folder 722)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Draft of Letter to Mayors, 1968 June 28 (Box 67, Folder 723)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Draft of Letter to Negro Publishers, 1968 June 26 (Box 67, Folder 724)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Five Former National Chairmans, Letter to Republican Convention Delegates, 1968 June 17 (Box 67, Folder 725)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Letters to Various Groups, Miscellaneous Messages, Telegrams, 1968 May 9-August 3 (Box 67, Folder 726)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Thirteen Short Statements, 1968 June 2 (Box 68, Folder 727)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Draft Rockefeller Card, undated (Box 68, Folder 728)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, "Let's Set the Record Straight", undated (Box 68, Folder 729)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Rockefeller Biography, "30 Years of Know-How", undated (Box 68, Folder 730)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, "The Truth about Nelson Rockefeller", 1968 June (Box 68, Folder 731)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, "Vote Power, Rockefeller vs Nixon", 1968 (Box 68, Folder 732)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, "Why Rockefeller", 1968 June (Box 68, Folder 733)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Michigan Delegation Questions and Answers, 1968 June 13 (Box 68, Folder 734)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Short Answers for Rockefeller to Questions most Frequently Asked, undated (Box 68, Folder 735)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, Speakers Kit, 1968 June 19 (Box 68, Folder 736)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Miscellaneous Informational Pieces, "Why Rockefeller" Useful Facts for Speakers, undated (Box 68, Folder 737)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Harvard Review, 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 738)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Look, "Why I seek the Presidency", 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 739)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Newsday, "Rebuilding Strife-Torn Cities", 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 740)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Young Republicans, "Republican Leadership, News for the Empire State, 1968 June (Box 68, Folder 741)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Ripon Society, "A Call for Pragmatism", 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 742)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Life, "Views on Presidency", 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 743)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, The Saturday Review, "My Concept of the Presidency", 1968 June 6 (Box 68, Folder 744)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Victor Riesel Column, "We can get the Country Back on Course", 1968 May (Box 68, Folder 745)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Articles for Publications, Christianity and Crisis, "Why I am for Nelson Rockefeller", undated (Box 68, Folder 746)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Memos, Schedules, 1968 May-July (Box 68, Folder 747)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Presidential Campaign, Press Releases and Speeches Pending, Proposed Speech on Conventional Arms, 1968 June 27 (Box 68, Folder 748)